Joseph Zhu

josephzuowork@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/josephzhu-/

SUMMARY

First ever concurrent enrolled Doctor of Medicine and Bachelor of Computer Science student at UNSW

Interested in clinical applications of AI to optimise healthcare resources, provide better patient education and support, and allow doctors to dedicate more time to research and innovation

Highly effective in both team and solo work scenarios with strong critical thinking, communication, analytical, and problem-solving skills

SKILLS

Skilled in C and Python **Strong Communication** Critical Thinking Fast Learner Flexible and Adaptable

LANGUAGES

English (Native) Mandarin (Native) French (Conversational)

ACADEMIC RESULTS

Current WAM - 83 (Med) 96 (CS) UCAT - 3350 4U Maths - 98 3U Maths - 99 American College Testing (ACT) - 36

PROJECTS

TBD

PUBLICATIONS

TBD

EDUCATION

University of New South Wales, NSW, Australia

Bachelor of Medical Studies and Doctor of Medicine Bachelor of Computer Science (Artificial Intelligence) 2024 - Present

2023 - Present

EXPERIENCE

EduVision, Sydney, NSW, Australia

Mathematics Consultant

2022 - Present

Developed and conducted extension Maths courses for Y5-8 students in preparation for AMC, AIMO, and beyond

UNSW Museum of Human Diseases, Sydney, NSW, Australia

2023 - Present

Museum Assistant

Guided high-school students and visitors in areas of Biology, Genetics, Pathology, Histology, and general Medicine

UNSW Food Hub, Sydney, NSW, Australia

2023

Volunteer

Coordinated with Foodbank in procuring and distributing foods and essential necessities for surrounding communities

Youth in Philanthropy, Southborough, MA, USA

2019

Committee member

Researched local charities, performed on-site evaluations with financial budgeting, and collaborated with surrounding communities to allocate funds and services for outreach

ACHIEVEMENTS

Scientia Scholar at UNSW for academic excellence